Jitendra Bordiya

Software Engineer

in Jitendra.Bordiya

Summary

**Having 2 yrs. of Experience as a NET Developer with Microsoft .NET Technologies in Asp. Net , MVC, C#, WCF Services, Web API, Net Core, MS SQL Server, Rest Services, Software Architecture. I am Actively looking for new opportunity that helps me to grow my technical skill that helps in the growth of organisation. **

Experience

Fendahl CTRM International 2021-11-08

Software Engineer Nagpur Maharatra,India

https://fendahl.com/

1. Contributed to Software design and development. 2. Diagnosed and resolved database defects, ensuring QA deployment stability. 3. Gathered development requirements, created physical data models, and designed database schema. 4. Debugged and fixed bugs in the existing project. 5. Conducted Unit Testing and participated in code reviews.

Thinkquotient Software Pvt Ltd

.NET Intern

2021-08-01 - 2021-11-01

Employee Appraisal System: Employee Appraisal System is a Console Based Application Which contains database of a Company Employee and Monitoring employee Performance and Appraisal History and Perform CRUD operation on Employee Information for ex. Add a new employee, Retreive Employee Information, Update Employee Information, Delete Existing Employee. Tech Tools: C#, SQL Server 2018, ADO.NET, Visual Studio 2019, Console App, GitHub.

Education

Sagar Institute of Research & Technology Excellence, Ayodhya Bypass Road, Bhopal -462041

2016-01-01 - 2020-01-01

Bachelor of Engineering - BE

Sanskar Academy High Secondary School

Science

2015-07-19 - 2016-07-19

HSC 64 %

Proiects

Pokemon Review APP

2023-06-01 - 2023-06-01

Pokémon Review API is a Web Api

https://github.com/JitendraBordiya/Pokemon-Review-APP

Pokémon review App is a Web Api which shows Pokémon details and owner information etc we can Add,update,delete and retrieve information. Technology and Tools: .NET Core 7 Web API, C#, SQL Server 2018, AutoMapper,JWT Bearer for Authentication,JSON,Visual Studio 2022.

Word Counter - APP 2023-06-01 - 2023-06-22

Word Counter is a React App

https://github.com/JitendraBordiya/ReactJs-WordsCounter

Word Counter is an app that count word in an article, Average read time, word preview and clear text screen, upper and lower case conversion of article. Technology: ReactJs, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3

Skills

.NET Framework	ASP.NET Core	ASP.NET MVC	ASP.NET Web API	Windows Communication Foundation (WCF)
HTML5	C#	Microsoft SQL Server	Entity Framework (EF Core)	Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)
jQuery	JSON	REST APIS		Visual Studio
JavaScript	Git	Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)		

Certifications

SOL Certificate 2021-12-01 HackerRank

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/b9dc914a8d18

SQL (intermediate) 2021-12-01

HackerRank

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/dfbd25b379af

Problem Solving (Basic) 2022-01-01 HackerRank

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/d7f6cfcd67be